question_data = {
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
            "question": "In the periodic table, Potassium&#039;s symbol is the letter K.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Animals",
            "question": "Rabbits are rodents.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "category": "Sports",
            "question": "ATP tennis hosted several tournaments on carpet court before being replaced to reduce injuries.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Sports",
            "question": "In association football, or soccer, a corner kick is when the game restarts after someone scores a goal.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Stevie Wonder&#039;s real name is Stevland Hardaway Morris.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Mythology",
            "question": "Janus was the Roman god of doorways and passageways.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
            "question": "Druid is a mage class in &quot;Log Horizon&quot;.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Film",
            "question": "Han Solo&#039;s co-pilot and best friend, &quot;Chewbacca&quot;, is an Ewok.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Film",
            "question": "George Lucas directed the entire original Star Wars trilogy.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Board Games",
            "question": "The Angry Video Game Nerd&#039;s alter ego is &quot;Board James&quot;.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        }
    ]
}

# new_list = []
#
# print(question_data["results"][0]["question"])
# print(question_data["results"][0]["correct_answer"])
#
# for question in question_data["results"]:
#     question_text = question["question"]
#     question_answer = question["correct_answer"]
#     print(question_text)
# print(new_list)
